<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2016-11-21T10:51:03-06:00</updated><id>//</id><title type="html">Civil Dissident</title><subtitle>Civil Dissident is committed to publishing dissenting opinions on everything. We believe that it is reckless and dangerous to hold beliefs that have never been challenged. Hence, we are committed foremost to questioning the establishment.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">What do Lemmings do? Why, they Lem!</title><link href="/dissent/against%20the%20establishment/against%20trump/2016/11/14/what-do-lemmings-do.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What do Lemmings do? Why, they Lem!" /><published>2016-11-14T15:54:56-06:00</published><updated>2016-11-14T15:54:56-06:00</updated><id>/dissent/against%20the%20establishment/against%20trump/2016/11/14/what-do-lemmings-do</id><content type="html" xml:base="/dissent/against%20the%20establishment/against%20trump/2016/11/14/what-do-lemmings-do.html">&lt;p&gt;I am angry. Do not tell me to feel otherwise. Dissent is healthy; dissent is good. Our republic cannot function correctly without a reasoned discourse of dissenting opinions, and that is why we have freedom of speech and freedom of press. I have a right to protest, and as long as we are threatened with injustice, I will exercise that right. Do not tell me there’s no point, because the act of dissent is its own point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If my opinion is unfounded, convince me otherwise. Frankly, I want to believe that this will be okay. I would love it if someone could convince me of that. But if Trump sticks with the platform he ran on, and appoints the cabinet rumored to be under consideration, then the nation is in peril. People are supposed to hope that a new president sticks to campaign promises, but I firmly believe the only hope for us is if he abandons most of his platform by the time he begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you deny that he is demagogue, you are a blind. If you deny that he is a hate-monger and a fear-monger, then you are a fool. If you deny the immense danger that comes with Donald Trump in the Oval, then you are a lemming, and I have a feeling that a reasoned discourse will be unsuccessful.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jordan Potarf</name><email>jordan_potarf@baylor.edu</email></author><category term="Dissent" /><category term="Trump" /><category term="Election2016" /><category term="Protest" /><category term="Ideals" /><summary type="html">I am angry. Do not tell me to feel otherwise. Dissent is healthy; dissent is good. Our republic cannot function correctly without a reasoned discourse of dissenting opinions, and that is why we have freedom of speech and freedom of press. I have a right to protest, and as long as we are threatened with injustice, I will exercise that right. Do not tell me there’s no point, because the act of dissent is its own point.</summary></entry></feed>
